Hello.
こんにちは
It's cute.
可愛いっすね
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Yeah.
うん
Are you used to cameras?
なんか カメラとか、慣れてるんでしょ?
That's not the case.
そんなことはないんで
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Yeah.
うん
How old are you now?
今はいくつですか?
I turned 20 last week.
先週20歳になりました
Oh, last week?
あ、先週?
Congratulations.
おめでとう
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Did you eat birthday cake?
バースデーケーキ食べましたか?
I haven't eaten.
食べてないです
fault.
あ ら
I want to eat it.
食べたいね
i want to eat.
食べたい
Did you have a birthday party?
誕生日会とかしなかった?
I haven't.
してないです
That's right.
そうなんだ
With my boyfriend.
彼氏と
Birthday party with my boyfriend.
彼氏と誕生日会
I don't have a boyfriend.
彼氏いないです
Isn't there?
ないんすか?
We were separated.
分かれちゃいました
Have you separated?
分かれちゃった?
yes.
はい
Why did we split up?
どうして分かれちゃったの?
We got into a fight.
喧嘩しちゃった
fight?
喧嘩?
That's a bit interesting, isn't it?
ちょっと興味深いですね、それは
What's the fight?
何喧嘩ですか?
There are discrepancies at first glance.
一見に食い違い
I guess that's true though.
それはそうなんだろうけど
How long have you been together?
どのくらい付き合ってたの?
It's not that long.
そんなに長くないです
Hmm.
うーん
What kind of person do you like?
ど んな人が好きなんですか?
kind person.
優しい人
They say you're a kind person.
優しい人って 言うよね
everyone.
みんな
That's true though.
それはそうなんだけど
What's next?
その次は?
Interesting person.
面白い人
What's next?
その次は?
Someone who is fun to be with.
一緒にいて楽しい人
After all, he's handsome, right?
結局イケメンでしょ?
That's not true.
そんなことないですよ
That's what I'll say.
それで言うね
If I had to choose between those three, I think the picture head is correct.
その3つで言ったら 絵頭とか 当てはまってるじゃん
It's certainly interesting.
確かに面白い
It's fun, I guess.
楽しいよ、多分
That would be kind.
優しいだろうし
Can I date a kind person?
優しい人と付き合えますか?
I don't understand.
分かんないです
分かんないよね
I've never met him before.
会 ったことないしね
wonderful.
素晴らしい
It seems impossible here.
ここで無理ですみたいな
I don't understand.
分かんないです
That's wonderful.
素晴らしいですね
Have you had sex recently?
最近エッチしました?
It's urgent though.
急ですけど
I haven't.
してないです
This was while I was doing it.
今のはしてる間でしたね
I haven't.
してないです
What is the average number of people?
平均人数は何ですか?
3 people.
3人
3 people?
3人?
Not 30 people or something.
30人とかじゃなくて
3 people, 3 people.
3人、3人
one hand.
片手
lie?
うそ?
Because it's very sexy.
色気がすごいから
Are you doing a lot?
いっぱいしてるのかな?
I haven't.
してないです
Is that the person you dated?
それは付き合った人?
Who have you dated so far?
今まで付き合った人?
that's right.
そうです
Ex-boyfriend.
元彼
Did you have a lot of sex with your ex-boyfriend?
元彼ともエッチいっぱいしました?
I don't do that much.
そんなにしてないですよ
You like sex, right?
エッチ好きでしょ?
That's not the case.
そんなことないです
What do you usually do now?
今普段は何してるんだっけ?
Work or something.
仕事とか
Female college student.
女子大生
You were active in the entertainment industry, right?
芸能活動してたでしょ?
that's right.
そうです
I was a backup dancer for an artist.
アーティストのバックダンサーしてました
That's amazing.
すごいね
Was there something on TV?
テレビとかでた?
It was out.
出てました
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
Live shows.
ライブとか
Is there such a thing as an artist?
言 える範囲でアーティストとかあります?
It's an idol type.
アイドル系です
That's right.
そうなんだ
Idol.
アイドル
That's amazing.
すごいね
If I appear once, do I get paid?
あるの1回出ると、 お金もらえんの?
That's not the case.
そんなことないです
Male artist?
男性アーティスト?
female artist.
女性アーティスト
That's amazing.
すごいね
As soon as we can talk to each other, right?
声かけ合えたらすぐでしょ?
There were a lot of cute kids there.
可愛い子たくさんいたから
It looks okay too.
見た目も大丈夫ね
Everyone is so cute.
みんな可愛いもんね
Everyone is cute.
みんな可愛い
Dancing in the background.
バックで踊ってる
Today is a dance audition.
今日はダンスオーディションということで
yes.
はい
I want to see some nice dancing.
素敵なダンスを見たいなと
I'm looking forward to it.
楽しみですね
Your eyesight is strong.
目力強めですね
Is it strong?
強いですか?
So cute.
可愛いな
The clothes are nice too.
服装もいいですね
What kind of edge do you like?
どういうエッジが好きですか?
What kind of edge?
どういうエッジ?
Yeah.
うん
Do you feel like you're being blamed?
責められる感じ?
I want to be blamed.
責められたい
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
Can I smell it?
匂い嗅いでいいですか?
I have a smell fetish.
匂いフェチなんですよ
is that so?
そうですか?
What what?
なになに?
what happened?
どうしたの?
I can go.
いける
Can you go?
いける?
I need to check it out a bit.
ちょっと確認しないと
Can I check?
確認していい?
For now.
とりあえずね
Like a greeting.
挨拶みたいな
greeting?
挨拶?
Ah, that's interesting to include.
あ、含めが面白い
I'm going to run out.
つぼっちゃう
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It doesn't smell.
匂いしないね
yes.
そう
The mask falls off.
覆面がつぼる
I don't see it.
見ないもんね
I like being blamed.
責められるの好きなの
It seems like I'm blaming you.
責めてそうだけどね
It smells good.
いい匂いしてる
intense.
激しい
That's erotic.
エ ロいね
I'm going to run out.
つぼっちゃう
nostalgic.
懐かしい
When was the last time you got hooked?
最近いつイッチしたの?
I don't know at all.
全然知ってない
Are you alone?
一人イッチは?
I don't know.
知ってない
TRUE?
本当?
Yeah.
うん
Oh, amazing.
あ、すげえ
That's amazing, that's amazing.
すげえすげえですよ
This is tempting.
これ誘惑してるな
Are you seducing me?
誘惑してる?
I'm seducing you.
誘惑してる
Is there a part of your heart that you like to be touched?
触られて心好きなところとかある?
Pikmin?
ピクミン?
I asked you to rephrase it.
言い換えてもらいましたけど
It suits you.
似合うね
Wow, your legs are so beautiful.
うわ、超足きれいじゃん
Wow, beautiful feet.
すげえ足きれい
It's smooth.
すべすべじゃん
nostalgic.
懐かしい
That's amazing.
すごいな
I can see it now.
今見えてるよ
nostalgic.
懐かしい
It's black.
黒いね
nostalgic.
懐かしい
It's black underwear.
黒い下着なんだ
I like black.
黒好きなんだ
黒好き
Her legs are white, so the contrast is amazing.
足が白いから、 対比がすごい
With black.
黒と
I'm doing an embarrassing pose.
恥ずかしいポーズしてる
It's white.
白いね
How about being touched here?
ここ触られるのどう?
Nice ass.
いいお尻
I have really nice feet.
めっちゃいい足にしてる
That's amazing.
す げえすげえですよ
Did you know?
知ってた?
i don't know.
知らない
i don't know?
知らない?
cute.
可愛い
It's super cute.
超可愛いね
Are you popular?
モテるっしょ?
To foreigners.
外人に
Take a look.
ちょっと目くって
My abdominal muscles are cracked.
腹筋割れてるね
on second thoughts.
や っぱり
beautiful.
きれい
As expected.
さすがだね
He's a professional.
プロだね
Do you have abs?
腹筋してる?
I don't know.
知ってないよ
That's amazing.
すごいな
Your butt is so curvy.
プリプリだね、お尻
So erotic.
すげえエロい
Spread your legs like before,
さっきみたいに、 足開いて、
I'll touch here alone
ここ 一人で触ってく
Because there are people who can.
れる 人がいるから
So beautiful.
すげえきれい
It's so beautiful.
めちゃめちゃきれいだね
Erotic.
エロい
Show me your side.
脇見せて
Start aside.
脇始める
Show me your side.
一緒に脇見せて
Can I take this home?
これ持って帰っていい?
No.
ダメ
beautiful.
きれい
It's not growing at all.
全然生えてないじゃん
It turned out to be round.
丸目になっちゃったね
Tiny.
ちっちゃ
Isn't it small?
ちっちゃくね?
Small?
ちっちゃい?
It's small.
ちっちゃいよ
It's super beautiful.
超きれいじゃん
nice.
いいね
cute.
かわいい